nootheme.com 2017-06-07

# Privacy - NooTheme

NooTheme (SITE) has established this privacy policy to demonstrate our commitment to the privacy of the users of our website. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy, and how we treat personally identifiable information collected from our visitors and users. While this isn’t the most glamorous of documents, privacy is a big concern these days, and we take it very seriously for you, our valued visitors.

### WHAT THIS PRIVACY POLICY COVERS

This privacy policy covers NooTheme treatment of personally identifiable information collected by NooTheme through a website owned and operated by NooTheme. This privacy policy does not apply to the practices of companies that NooTheme does not own or control, or of persons that NooTheme does not employ or manage, including any third-party content contributors bound by contract and any third-party websites to which the SITE may link.

### COLLECTION & USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

You can visit the website of NooTheme without revealing any personal information. However, NooTheme needs certain personal information if you wish to purchase certain products, receive our newsletter, or use certain NooTheme services.

Where required, this information may include your personal contact information and/or your company contact information. NooTheme will use this information to reply to your inquiries, to provide you with requested products and services, and to contact you regarding new products and services. By accessing the services of NooTheme and voluntarily providing us with the requested personal information, you consent to the collection and use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

### COLLECTION & USE OF NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION

NooTheme automatically receives and records non-personal information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information, and the page you requested. NooTheme may use this information to customize the content you see and to fulfill your requests for certain products and services. However, NooTheme does not connect this non-personal data to any personal information collected from you.

### INFORMATION SHARING & DISCLOSURE

NooTheme will not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### CONSENT

If you do not consent to the collection, use or disclosure of your personal information as outlined in this policy, please do not provide any personal information to NooTheme. If you have provided personal information to NooTheme and no longer consent to its use or disclosure as outlined herein, please notify us.

### SECURITY

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be considered 100% secure. However, your NooTheme information is protected for your privacy and security. In certain areas of our websites, as identified on the site, NooTheme may use industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions. We also safeguard your personal information from unauthorized access through access control procedures and physical security measures. Further, NooTheme retains your personal information only as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes identified above or as required by law.

### CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

NooTheme may at any time, without notice to you and in its sole discretion, amend this policy from time to time. When it does, NooTheme will also revise the “last update” date at the top of this Privacy Policy. Please review this policy periodically. Your continued use of the SITE after any such amendments signifies your acceptance thereof.

### QUESTIONS OR SUGGESTIONS

If you have questions or suggestions about this privacy policy, or your own personal information, please contact us directly.
